<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Front Jus</title>
	<atom:link href="https://front.jus.com.br/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://front.jus.com.br</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:51:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Spotlight on Excellence: The 96th Academy Awards Await</title>
		<link>https://front.jus.com.br/spotlight-on-excellence-the-96th-academy-awards-await/</link>
					<comments>https://front.jus.com.br/spotlight-on-excellence-the-96th-academy-awards-await/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[96th Academy Awards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oscar]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://front.jus.com.br/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Introduction: In the dazzling world of cinema, the countdown has begun for the most prestigious event of the year—the 96th Academy Awards. As Hollywood&#8217;s brightest stars gather, and the red carpet is rolled out, anticipation fills the air for an evening that will honor outstanding achievements in filmmaking. Body: *1. A Year of Cinematic Brilliance: [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Introduction:</strong> In the dazzling world of cinema, the countdown has begun for the most prestigious event of the year—the 96th Academy Awards. As Hollywood&#8217;s brightest stars gather, and the red carpet is rolled out, anticipation fills the air for an evening that will honor outstanding achievements in filmmaking.</p>



<p><strong>Body:</strong></p>



<p>*1. <strong>A Year of Cinematic Brilliance:</strong> The 96th Academy Awards arrive on the heels of a cinematic year that has left an indelible mark on the industry. From compelling dramas to boundary-pushing blockbusters, this year&#8217;s nominations reflect the diverse and powerful narratives that captivated audiences worldwide. Join us as we celebrate the creative brilliance that defines the landscape of contemporary cinema.</p>



<p>*2. <strong>Star-Studded Red Carpet Extravaganza:</strong> The red carpet is not just a walkway; it&#8217;s a canvas where fashion meets artistry. Hollywood&#8217;s A-listers, draped in glamorous attire, will grace the red carpet with style and panache. From stunning gowns to tailored tuxedos, the fashion statements at the Oscars are as much a part of the spectacle as the awards themselves.</p>



<p>*3. <strong>Nominees Who Dazzled and Directors Who Soared:</strong> The nominees for the 96th Academy Awards represent a tapestry of talent. Actors who brought characters to life, directors who crafted cinematic masterpieces, and artists who painted the screen with their creativity—all will be recognized for their contributions to the world of film. Join us as we applaud the nominees who brought stories to life and the directors who skillfully guided these narratives.</p>



<p>*4. <strong>Cinematic Diversity in the Limelight:</strong> The Oscars continue to be a beacon for diversity and inclusion in the film industry. This year&#8217;s nominations showcase a rich mosaic of voices from various backgrounds, shedding light on stories that resonate across cultures. As we witness the awards unfold, let&#8217;s celebrate the industry&#8217;s commitment to fostering an inclusive and representative cinematic landscape.</p>



<p>*5. <strong>Unforgettable Moments and Speeches:</strong> Beyond the awards, the Oscars are a stage for unforgettable moments and heartfelt speeches. From emotional expressions of gratitude to powerful calls for change, the ceremony often becomes a platform for artists to use their voices. Tune in as we capture the essence of these poignant moments that transcend the silver screen.</p>



<p><strong>Conclusion:</strong> As the curtain rises on the 96th Academy Awards, let&#8217;s immerse ourselves in an evening that pays tribute to the magic of storytelling and the artists who bring these stories to life. Join us for live coverage, behind-the-scenes glimpses, and a front-row seat to the celebration of excellence in cinema.</p>



<p><strong>Date and Venue:</strong> The 96th Academy Awards will take place on March 10, 2024 at Dolby Theatre Hollywood, Los Angeles, California, U.S.. Stay tuned for a night of glamour, surprises, and the crowning of this year&#8217;s cinematic champions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://front.jus.com.br/spotlight-on-excellence-the-96th-academy-awards-await/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Record in K-pop history, 11 million albums sold in 11 months</title>
		<link>https://front.jus.com.br/record-in-k-pop-history-11-million-albums-sold-in-11-months/</link>
					<comments>https://front.jus.com.br/record-in-k-pop-history-11-million-albums-sold-in-11-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreign songs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kpop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[V BTS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://front.jus.com.br/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sales of K-pop albums (DVDs and vinyl records) are booming in South Korea. In the 11 months from January to November this year, 11.16 million copies of the album were sold in the country. News from Korea Jungang Daily The press reported on the circle chart that, before adding December&#8217;s figures, 144 percent more albums [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sales of K-pop albums (DVDs and vinyl records) are booming in South Korea. In the 11 months from January to November this year, 11.16 million copies of the album were sold in the country. News from Korea Jungang Daily</p>



<p>The press reported on the circle chart that, before adding December&#8217;s figures, 144 percent more albums were sold this year than last year. 8 crore albums were sold last year.</p>



<p>This is the first time in South Korean history to reach the milestone of over 100 million album sales in a single year. While DVD sales are falling amid the digital album boom around the world, the picture is different in Korea. People of the country are still rushing to buy DVDs due to the K-pop craze.</p>



<p>More than 1.5 million albums were sold this November alone; It is also the highest for the month. Circle Chart said that more than one crore albums were sold in six months this year. But last year, one crore albums were sold in just one month. &#8216;Stray Kids&#8217; topped album sales in November this year. Albums by Jangkook, V, Infaifen, Jirobeswan, NCT Dream, Seventeen topped the list in the last 11 months.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://front.jus.com.br/record-in-k-pop-history-11-million-albums-sold-in-11-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shahid bought this car for 4.5 million taka</title>
		<link>https://front.jus.com.br/shahid-bought-this-car-for-4-5-million-taka/</link>
					<comments>https://front.jus.com.br/shahid-bought-this-car-for-4-5-million-taka/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bollywood star]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shahid Kapoor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the star]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://front.jus.com.br/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shahid Kapoor is one of the hot stars of Bollywood. But his car hobby is a bit more. This Bollywood actor&#8217;s garage is adorned with numerous prestigious cars. This time Mercedes Maybach GLS 600 has been added to this list. He recently bought this car and now he is in discussion.Anyone&#8217;s eyes will be dazzled [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Shahid Kapoor is one of the hot stars of Bollywood. But his car hobby is a bit more. This Bollywood actor&#8217;s garage is adorned with numerous prestigious cars. This time Mercedes Maybach GLS 600 has been added to this list. He recently bought this car and now he is in discussion.<br>Anyone&#8217;s eyes will be dazzled by Shahid&#8217;s car collection. Now another expensive car has been added to his garage. This Bollywood star bought the Mercedes Mayback GLS 600 car and is now practicing.</p>



<p>Maybach India shared an image on their official page. Shahid and his wife Mira Rajput are seen standing in front of their new car with &#8216;goodies&#8217; in their hands. The picture of this star couple has spread in the net world. Net Janata congratulates Shahid and Meera for buying a new car.</p>



<p>The price of the elite Mercedes Maybach GLS 600 car is said to be four and a half crores in Bangladeshi currency. Last year, Shahid bought a Mercedes Maybach S580. The price of this car was around 2.8 crores. Apart from this, Shahid&#8217;s car collection includes famous cars like Range Rover Vogue, Porsche Scion GTS, Jaguar XKR-S, Mercedes-AMG S400. Each of its cars cost more than crores of rupees.</p>



<p>Mercedes Maybach GLS 600 car has been bought by Ranveer Singh, Arjun Kapoor, Kriti Shannon, Neetu Singh. This time the owner of this expensive car is Shahid. This Bollywood star made his debut in OTT this year. He was seen in OTT projects &#8216;Forgy&#8217; and &#8216;Bloody Daddy&#8217;. He is all set to hit the big screen next year with Kriti Shannon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://front.jus.com.br/shahid-bought-this-car-for-4-5-million-taka/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>After 12 years of love, two producers got married</title>
		<link>https://front.jus.com.br/after-12-years-of-love-two-producers-got-married/</link>
					<comments>https://front.jus.com.br/after-12-years-of-love-two-producers-got-married/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[star wedding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the star]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://front.jus.com.br/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8216;Barbie&#8217; creator Greta Gerwig is married to longtime partner, producer Noah Baumbach. They have been together for almost a century; This couple has given form to the relationship of love.The American magazine People reported that they got married in a domestic ceremony at the New York City Hall. The story of the popular movie &#8216;Barbie&#8217; [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8216;Barbie&#8217; creator Greta Gerwig is married to longtime partner, producer Noah Baumbach. They have been together for almost a century; This couple has given form to the relationship of love.<br>The American magazine People reported that they got married in a domestic ceremony at the New York City Hall. The story of the popular movie &#8216;Barbie&#8217; was jointly written by Noah Baumbach and Greta Gerwig.</p>



<p>They met while working in the movie &#8216;Greenbird&#8217; in 2010; 40-year-old Greta and 54-year-old Noah have been in a relationship since 2011. Their first child Harold Ralph was born in 2019. In an interview given to Elle UK last July, Greta Gerwig said that their second child was born in February this year.<br>The pair received an Oscar nomination in 2020; Noah with &#8216;Marriage Story&#8217; and Greta with &#8216;Little Women&#8217; walked the Oscars red carpet.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://front.jus.com.br/after-12-years-of-love-two-producers-got-married/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://front.jus.com.br/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://front.jus.com.br/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://front.jus.com.br/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://front.jus.com.br/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
