<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Shahid Kapoor &#8211; Front Jus</title>
	<atom:link href="https://front.jus.com.br/tag/shahid-kapoor/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://front.jus.com.br</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:43:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Shahid bought this car for 4.5 million taka</title>
		<link>https://front.jus.com.br/shahid-bought-this-car-for-4-5-million-taka/</link>
					<comments>https://front.jus.com.br/shahid-bought-this-car-for-4-5-million-taka/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bollywood star]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shahid Kapoor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the star]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://front.jus.com.br/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Shahid Kapoor is one of the hot stars of Bollywood. But his car hobby is a bit more. This Bollywood actor&#8217;s garage is adorned with numerous prestigious cars. This time Mercedes Maybach GLS 600 has been added to this list. He recently bought this car and now he is in discussion.Anyone&#8217;s eyes will be dazzled [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Shahid Kapoor is one of the hot stars of Bollywood. But his car hobby is a bit more. This Bollywood actor&#8217;s garage is adorned with numerous prestigious cars. This time Mercedes Maybach GLS 600 has been added to this list. He recently bought this car and now he is in discussion.<br>Anyone&#8217;s eyes will be dazzled by Shahid&#8217;s car collection. Now another expensive car has been added to his garage. This Bollywood star bought the Mercedes Mayback GLS 600 car and is now practicing.</p>



<p>Maybach India shared an image on their official page. Shahid and his wife Mira Rajput are seen standing in front of their new car with &#8216;goodies&#8217; in their hands. The picture of this star couple has spread in the net world. Net Janata congratulates Shahid and Meera for buying a new car.</p>



<p>The price of the elite Mercedes Maybach GLS 600 car is said to be four and a half crores in Bangladeshi currency. Last year, Shahid bought a Mercedes Maybach S580. The price of this car was around 2.8 crores. Apart from this, Shahid&#8217;s car collection includes famous cars like Range Rover Vogue, Porsche Scion GTS, Jaguar XKR-S, Mercedes-AMG S400. Each of its cars cost more than crores of rupees.</p>



<p>Mercedes Maybach GLS 600 car has been bought by Ranveer Singh, Arjun Kapoor, Kriti Shannon, Neetu Singh. This time the owner of this expensive car is Shahid. This Bollywood star made his debut in OTT this year. He was seen in OTT projects &#8216;Forgy&#8217; and &#8216;Bloody Daddy&#8217;. He is all set to hit the big screen next year with Kriti Shannon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://front.jus.com.br/shahid-bought-this-car-for-4-5-million-taka/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
