<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>kpop &#8211; Front Jus</title>
	<atom:link href="https://front.jus.com.br/tag/kpop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://front.jus.com.br</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:46:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Record in K-pop history, 11 million albums sold in 11 months</title>
		<link>https://front.jus.com.br/record-in-k-pop-history-11-million-albums-sold-in-11-months/</link>
					<comments>https://front.jus.com.br/record-in-k-pop-history-11-million-albums-sold-in-11-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foreign songs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kpop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[V BTS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://front.jus.com.br/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sales of K-pop albums (DVDs and vinyl records) are booming in South Korea. In the 11 months from January to November this year, 11.16 million copies of the album were sold in the country. News from Korea Jungang Daily The press reported on the circle chart that, before adding December&#8217;s figures, 144 percent more albums [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sales of K-pop albums (DVDs and vinyl records) are booming in South Korea. In the 11 months from January to November this year, 11.16 million copies of the album were sold in the country. News from Korea Jungang Daily</p>



<p>The press reported on the circle chart that, before adding December&#8217;s figures, 144 percent more albums were sold this year than last year. 8 crore albums were sold last year.</p>



<p>This is the first time in South Korean history to reach the milestone of over 100 million album sales in a single year. While DVD sales are falling amid the digital album boom around the world, the picture is different in Korea. People of the country are still rushing to buy DVDs due to the K-pop craze.</p>



<p>More than 1.5 million albums were sold this November alone; It is also the highest for the month. Circle Chart said that more than one crore albums were sold in six months this year. But last year, one crore albums were sold in just one month. &#8216;Stray Kids&#8217; topped album sales in November this year. Albums by Jangkook, V, Infaifen, Jirobeswan, NCT Dream, Seventeen topped the list in the last 11 months.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://front.jus.com.br/record-in-k-pop-history-11-million-albums-sold-in-11-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
